[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is orange the national color of the Netherlands?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Leroys nemesis in the martial arts movie The Last Dragon?", "correct_answer": "Shonuff", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny", "Laura", "Mr. Miyagi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars character said, You have interfered with our affairs for the last time?", "correct_answer": "Count Dukoo", "incorrect_answers": ["Mace Windu", "Yoda", "Darth Maul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a term used for the building in which maple syrup is boiled?", "correct_answer": "Sugar Barn", "incorrect_answers": ["Sugarhouse", "Cabane a sucre", "Sugar Shanty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Prior to the awards in 2007, when was the last movie in which co-stars won the Oscars for Best Actor and Best Actress?", "correct_answer": "As Good As It Gets", "incorrect_answers": ["Titanic", "The Silence of the Lambs", "PeeWee Hermans Great Adventure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The average size of a normal human eye is commonly compared to the size of this object.", "correct_answer": "Golf ball", "incorrect_answers": ["Apricot", "Walnut", "Cherry tomato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many commercial maple syrup producers are there in North America?", "correct_answer": "16,000", "incorrect_answers": ["5,000", "12,000", "20,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It can reach an age far greater than that of any other living thing known - up to nearly 5,000 years.", "correct_answer": "Bristlecone Pine", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sequoia", "Redwood", "Western Mushroom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jose Raul Capablanca of Cuba was the first person from the Western Hemisphere to do what?", "correct_answer": "Win the World Chess Championship", "incorrect_answers": ["Be President of the U.N. General  Assembly", "Win an Olympic  baseball game", "Win the Nobel Prize for Literature"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which royal abode has had visitations from the ghosts of Thomas Becket, Anne Boleyn, King Henry VIII and Lady Jane Grey amongst many others (including a bear)?", "correct_answer": "The Tower of London", "incorrect_answers": ["Windsor Castle", "Sandringham", "Buckingham Palace"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Both Newton and Leibnitz claimed credit for inventing\u201d calculus. Which statement about calculus is true?", "correct_answer": "Whoever invented it, we use Leibnitz notation.", "incorrect_answers": ["Gauss really invented it.", "Euler really invented it.", "Whoever invented it, we use Newton\u2019s notation."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of insects are yellowjackets which live in colonies and build globular paper nests?", "correct_answer": "wasps", "incorrect_answers": ["ants", "crickets", "butterflies"]}]